[
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "The dog went for him.",
      "optionA": "a) The dog barked at him.",
      "optionB": "b) The dog attacked him.",
      "optionC": "c) The dog followed him.",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "I feel for you.",
      "optionA": "a) I am fond of you.",
      "optionB": "b) I pity you.",
      "optionC": "c) I sympathise for you.",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "She got over her illness.",
      "optionA": "a) She learned from her ilness.",
      "optionB": "b) She died from her ilness.",
      "optionC": "c) She recovered from her illness.",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
  "question":
  {
     "prompt": "The police looked into it.",
     "optionA": "a) The police didn't care about it.",
     "optionB": "b) The police ivestigated it.",
     "optionC": "c) The police looked inside it.",
     "rightOption": "b"
  }
},
{
   "question":
   {
     "prompt": "She came up with the solution.",
     "optionA": "a) She refused the solution.",
     "optionB": "b) She thought of the solution.",
     "optionC": "c) She couldn't understand the solution.",
     "rightOption": "b"
   }
 },
 {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "It was easy to find out the answer.",
      "optionA": "a) It was easy to forget the answer.",
      "optionB": "b) It was easy to share the answer.",
      "optionC": "c) It was easy to discover the answer.",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "When are we setting up the next meeting?",
      "optionA": "a) When are we recording the next meeting?",
      "optionB": "b) When are we arranging the next meeting?",
      "optionC": "c) When are we beginning the next meeting?",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
   },
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"You'll be able ___ that book out of the library.",
			"optionA":"to take",
			"optionB":"to bring",
			"optionC":"to move",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"We have ___ ahead if we want the party to be a success.",
			"optionA":"to go",
			"optionB":"to plan",
			"optionC":"to push",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She didn't say goodbye before ___ off. She must be upset.",
			"optionA":"she switched",
			"optionB":"she cut",
			"optionC":"she rang",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He decided ___ it down, althouhg it was a good job offer.",
			"optionA":"to turn",
			"optionB":"to pass",
			"optionC":"to take",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"When I saw his awful haircut I burst ___ laughing.",
			"optionA":"into",
			"optionB":"burst",
			"optionC":"in",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"As time ___ we do more damage to the environment.",
			"optionA":"goes beyond",
			"optionB":"goes forward",
			"optionC":"goes by",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She has decided to take ___ a new hobby.",
			"optionA":"up",
			"optionB":"over",
			"optionC":"on",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Could you repeat? I couldn't ___ what you said.",
			"optionA":"make up",
			"optionB":"make out",
			"optionC":"make over",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]
